Please sit in the waiting room over there, Mrs. Iwakura.
So... Ms. Iwakura, please wait there in the waiting room.
Lain, there's no need to be worried.
Lain, δε χρειάζεται να ανησυχείς τόσο πολύ.
Come, take a seat over here.
Παρακαλώ κάθισε εκεί.
Ah... would you like a juice or something to drink?
Α... θα ήθελες λίγο χυμό ή κάτι άλλο να πιεις;
If you don't, that's fine as well.
Είναι εντάξει αν δε θέλεις κάτι. Μην ανησυχείς.
Let me see...
Για να δούμε...
I'm thirsty, so I'll probably make some black tea. Would you like to join me, Lain?
Διψάω, οπότε πάω για τσάι... Θα ήθελες να έρθεις μαζί μου;
It'd be odd if I was the only one with a drink, right?
Γιατί θα φανεί περίεργο αν πίνω μόνο εγώ.
Thank you.
Σ' ευχαριστώ.
What would you like?
Ποιο από αυτά θέλεις;
I have all kinds of drinks.
Έχουμε πολλά για να διαλέξουμε.
Whatever you're having.
Το ίδιο με εσάς.
You want tea as well?
Μαύρο τσάι;
Wonderful!
Κατάλαβα.
Give me just a moment...
Μια στιγμή...
You can add sugar and milk as well, if you'd like.
Μπορείς να βάλεις ζάχαρη και γάλα αν θέλεις.
Here.
Ορίστε.
Not bad, huh?
Not bad, huh?
Earl Gray - it's one of my favorites.
Earl Grey τσάι, το λατρεύω.
Earl Grey?
Earl Grey;
Right.
Σωστά.
There are many different types of tea, all with different smells and tastes.
Ακόμα και με το τσάι υπάρχουν πολλά είδη, με διαφορετικά αρώματα και γεύσεις.
Is it good?
Έχει ωραία γεύση;
Well...
Λοιπόν...
I think it's very good,
Ταιριάζει στο γούστο μου.
but I don't know what your taste is like.
Αλλά δεν είμαι σίγουρη για 'σένα, Lain.
Drink a little bit and see if you like it.
Αν θέλεις, μπορείς να πιεις λίγο.
If it doesn't taste good, we can always make you something else, right?
Αν δε σου αρέσει, μπορώ να σου φτιάξω κάτι άλλο.
Here you go.
Ορίστε...